http://www.nsasoft.us/privacy_policy/

Privacy PolicyYou are here: Home / Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy
in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and make use
of personal information. The following outlines our Privacy Policy.
When accessing our Website, Nsasoft Us, LLC will learn certain information about
you during your visit.
Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology
called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?")
and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information
gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of
visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited
just before and just after our Web site, your IP address.
What Are Cookies?
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique
identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer
for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically
designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser
if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser
only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not
the cookies sent to you by other sites.
IP Addresses
IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the
Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network
to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web
server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data”
so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.
Email Information
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content
of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We
provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ
in the maintenance of information received online, mail and telephone.
How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering
our business activities, providing customer service and making available other
items and services to our customers and prospective customers.
Nsasoft Us, LLC will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you
visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor will
such information be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties
without the approval of the user at the time of collection.
We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words,
when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection
of our legal rights.
A Special Note About Children
Children are not eligible to use our web site and services and we ask that
minors (under the age of 13) do not submit any personal information to us. If
you are a minor, you can use this site only in conjunction with permission and
guidance from your parents or guardians.
How Do We Protect Your Information and Secure Information Transmissions?
Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason,
we request that you do not send private information to us by email. However,
doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Some of the information you may enter
on our Web site may be transmitted securely via a secure medium known as Secure
Sockets Layer, or SSL. Credit Card information is never transmitted via email.
Nsasoft Us, LLC may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used
for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections
of our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technical
design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.
For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available
to all users, Nsasoft Us, LLC uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify
unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.
Policy Changes
We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without
notice. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the
future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under
this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy
Policy, without your prior consent.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles
in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected
and maintained.
Contact
If you have any questions regarding this Policy, or your dealings with our
web site, please contact us.
End User License Agreement
End User License Agreement (EULA)
Tabs
Tabs (Content Tabs)
Team Element
Team Member
Terms of Service
Terms of Service (TOS)
Become an Affiliate
Followon TwitterSubscribeto RSS FeedLatest NewsTop Password Recovery RequestsJuly 1, 2011 - 6:57 pmNetwork Security News – Network Security MagazineJuly 1, 2011 - 6:57 pmResources Nsasoft Websites
Security Magazines
Customer Support Our support Hotline is available 24/7 Hours a day: (818) 850 6642
Contact Us
7ads6x98y
Scroll to top
